I'm home.
What time is it?
17:00!
What time is the bullet train today?
What time is the Shinkansen today? What time is the bullet train today? 7:30 in the morning? 7:30 a.m.? What time is the bullet train at?
7:00 a.m.?
7:30!
It was 7:30!
Already 10 hours!
You haven't stopped once today, you've been moving all day!
I haven't even eaten lunch yet!
How is Osaka after a long time?
It's fun to go to the right side of the city after a long day, it feels different!
I'll be back in the spring for some more games.
You can start with "Yoshi yoshi yoshi" first.
What do you mean?
Yes, yes...
First we play rock, paper, scissors.
Okay.
Turn around and look at me!
What do you want? It's almost my birthday.
I want a cheat honor.
Cool! You're cool.
Why is that?
Because the other members of Love One are sucking up to you.
No, they don't!
I respect you very much, very much.
Rock, paper, scissors.
First, we play rock-paper-scissors-scissors.
First, Kana.
First, Goo, rock-paper-scissors-scissors. That's how it started,
We decided to make it a brand, and we are now in the process of making various things.
There are no rules.
Well, you win if you get the same number.
So it's a communication game.
It's not a game of rock-paper-scissors.
We just finished a one-day promotion today.
I've been doing a lot of filming.
I've been doing a lot of filming and interviews and taping.
It was a really
It was a really intense day.
I'm going out for dinner now, and I'm going to eat teppanyaki, and it's 16 degrees, so it's been a really intense day.
I'm going out for dinner now.
I'm going to eat teppanyaki!
I've only had tofu yaki in Tokyo.
This protein in the sky is totally creepy!
It's 0:14 at the moment, but if we're going to have dinner here, then...
I need to finish up, right?
I'll have some then!
It's so good!
It's the first time I've been to Osaka in the summer.
I hope you're all here.
All of our members...
I'm sure you're all fired up.
Kimiyu Fuisaki...
She seemed tired.
She was sleeping all the time at the hotel.
I had dinner with the staff
We had dinner together.
We went out to dinner.
For Kimiyu Fuisaki
We had a luxurious time!
Thank you very much for your hospitality. I'm QCYM
Hello, hello, hello.
This time...
I'm here in Osaka.
Today.
I made bangs.
It's a limited edition.
Please give me your daily thoughts today.
Please, please, please, please, today I'm going to do my best to enjoy this morning after a long time.
I'll do my best
Let's do our best
Yuna is doing my hair today.
She's my exclusive hair stylist.
I'll ask her to do my hair.
I'm sure I'll think of something today.
I really hate my hairline!
Roo-chan's...
She said she hates my whimsical whimsical shape.
A whirligig
I'm sad
Whip whip whip whip
Love me on the whip too!
Right here.
I'm not in the middle.
Like this, not in the middle.
I know it's not in the middle.
I know, I know. My quirky little quirky little quirky little quirky little quirky little quirky little quirky little hair.
This hair is cute, too.
I'm going to have to do a lot of Lilly Swings and stuff like that.
I'm going to change my life today.
That's how I feel.
Hello everyone let's go to the hottest venue in the world, Wheel!
Hello everyone, hello everyone, thank you very much for your hard work, Okinawa is super bad, oh no, oh no, oh no!
This is the choreography for the song "Overwhelming Love"!
Let's do it together!
You're so cute!
Thank you very much. Cute. How about the second time in Osaka?
I want to eat something delicious.
Have you been to Osaka?
I've been here a few times.
This is my first time in Nagoya.
What would you like to eat?
Miso pork cutlet.
Tebasaki (chicken wings) are also delicious.
Mm-hmm.
I want a snack!
That's right.
I want some okonomiyaki, too.
I know.
I'm sorry, but...
Some kind of okonomiyaki
Tompeyaki.
It was really good, wasn't it?
It was delicious.
I want some!
Icichan is hugging you.
It's soooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooo cold!
It's windy, it's windy, it's cold, it's windy, it's cold, it's windy, it's cold, it's windy
It's so cold!
He's so cute!
Yay!
Bonchise beads are the best!
New
Pink Light Blue Gray
pink light blue-gray, sure vs.
Yuna is the prettiest!
Yuna is the cutest!
Ha-ha-ha-ha
I never said that.
Yuna, Yuna too
Good morning
Yuna is the cutest.
Yuna is the prettiest.
What?
I think you're prejudiced against my Yuna.
Are you imitating me?
You did it, Seira!
Make him my brother Sasaki, Sasaki!
I only eat vegetables
You're prejudiced.
Luna?
Am I the cutest?
No, Hina-chan is Hina-chan, and Hina-chan is Hina-chan. No, Yuna-chan is Yuna-chan.
Hina-chan is the cutest, right?
Right? We're the same.
Hinachan's good at mimicking Hina-chan.
Kagami.
What? Runo's cute!
The one you're saying.
Oh my God!
He's cute.
Is it?
Yeah.
You did it just now? You did it just now.
Easy is the cutest. Oh my God. He's really big.
Can I put it on the side? Big.
Thank you very much.
It's over.
The event is over.
Thank you very much.
It was fun, wasn't it?
It was fun.
I wish you could have made it longer. It was fun.
It was fun, wasn't it?
That particular Osaka was great, too, wasn't it?
It was great.
Osaka was great.
Let's go in the spring and fall next time.
I'll come.
I'll come. For sure.
Then we should come again soon.
I'll be back.
Bye bye.
bye-bye.